couponingtobedebtfree.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy and Cookie Policy

###### _(This post may include affiliate links which means we may earn a small commission from the advertiser when you click through our links. See our disclosure policy[here](https://www.couponingtobedebtfree.com/disclosuredisclaimer/).)_

Couponing to be Debt Free values your privacy and are committed to protecting it. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you of what information we may collect and how it may be used. If you don’t agree with this policy please immediately stop using our site.

**What information do we collect?**

  * We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.
  * When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

To send periodic emails

  * The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**Do we use cookies?**

  * Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information
  * We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
  * Our Coupons.com page uses third-party cookies and similar technologies.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 18 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [websites privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 5/24/18

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or wish to contact us regarding your personal data, please contact me at the following address or email address:

Couponing to be Debt Free, LLC  
4905 Middlesex Drive  
Louisville, KY 40245  
julia@couponingtobedebtfree.com
